<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<FrameLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
            <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView4" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="180dp" android:layout_marginBottom="-16dp" android:src="@drawable/evaclogo_2"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="23sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/black" android:gravity="center_horizontal" android:id="@+id/textView" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="Disaster Preparedness Tips" android:textAllCaps="true" android:textAlignment="center"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="20sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/black" android:gravity="center_horizontal" android:id="@+id/textView4" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="Typhoon Preparedness Tips" android:textAlignment="center"/>
            <HorizontalScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_margin="10dp">
                <RelativeLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                    <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView2" android:layout_width="380dp" android:layout_height="450dp" android:src="@drawable/disaster1"/>
                    <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView3" android:layout_width="340dp" android:layout_height="700dp" android:src="@drawable/typhoon1" android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/imageView2"/>
                    <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView5" android:layout_width="380dp" android:layout_height="550dp" android:src="@drawable/typhoon2" android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/imageView3"/>
                    <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView6" android:layout_width="350dp" android:layout_height="650dp" android:src="@drawable/typhoon3" android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/imageView5"/>
                    <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView7" android:layout_width="380dp" android:layout_height="480dp" android:src="@drawable/flooding1" android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/imageView6"/>
                </RelativeLayout>
            </HorizontalScrollView>
            <TextView android:textSize="15sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="10dp" android:paddingTop="10dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="BEFORE A TYPHOON HITS"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="16sp" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="15dp" android:paddingRight="15dp" android:paddingBottom="15dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="\10To prepare for a Typhoon, you should take the following measures:\10\10 1. To begin preparing, you should build an emergency kit and make a family communications plan.\10 2. Know your surroundings.\10 3. Learn the elevation level of your property and whether the land is flood-prone. This will help you know how your property will be affected when storm surge or tidal flooding are forecast.\10 4. Identify levees and dams in your area and determine whether they pose a hazard to you.\10 5. Learn community Typhoon evacuation routes and how to find higher ground. Determine where you would go and how you would get there if you needed to evacuate.\10 \10Make plans to secure your property:\10\10 1. Cover all of your home’s windows. Permanent storm shutters offer the best protection for windows. A second option is to board up windows with 5/8” marine plywood, cut to fit and ready to install. Tape does not prevent windows from breaking.\10 2. Install straps or additional clips to securely fasten your roof to the frame structure. This will reduce roof damage.\10 3. Be sure trees and shrubs around your home are well trimmed so they are more wind resistant.\10 4. Clear loose and clogged rain gutters and downspouts.\10 5. Reinforce your garage doors; if wind enters a garage it can cause dangerous and expensive structural damage.\10 6. Plan to bring in all outdoor furniture, decorations, garbage cans and anything else that is not tied down.\10 7. In a strong typhoon, A LOOSE OBJECT IS A MISSILE!\10 8. Determine how and where to secure your boat.\10 9. If in a high-rise building, be prepared to take shelter on or below the 10th floor."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="15sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="10dp" android:paddingTop="10dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="DURING A TYPHOON"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="16sp" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="15dp" android:paddingRight="15dp" android:paddingBottom="15dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="\10If a Typhoon is likely in your area, you should:\10\10 1.Listen to the radio or TV for information.\10 2. Secure your home, close storm shutters and secure outdoor objects or bring them indoors.\10 3. Turn off utilities (electricity) if instructed to do so. Otherwise, turn the refrigerator thermostat to its coldest setting and keep its doors closed.\10 4. Turn off LPG tanks\10 5. Avoid using the phone, except for serious emergencies.\10 6. Moor your boat if time permits.\10 7. Ensure a supply of water for sanitary purpose such as cleaning and flushing toilets. Fill the bathtub and other larger containers with water.\10 8. Find out how to keep food safe during and after and emergency.\10 \10 You should evacuate under the following conditions:\10\10 - If you are directed by local authorities to do so. Be sure to follow their instructions.\10 - If you live in a weak home or temporary structure, such shelter are particularly hazardous during Typhoon no matter how well fastened to the ground.\10 - If you live in a high-rise building – Typhoon winds are stronger at higher elevations.\10 - If you live on the coast, on a floodplain, near a river, or on an island waterway."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="15sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="10dp" android:paddingTop="10dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="AFTER A TYPHOON PASSES..."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="16sp" android:textColor="@color/black" android:paddingLeft="15dp" android:paddingRight="15dp" android:paddingBottom="15dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="\101. Continue listening to Radio or the local news for the latest updates.\10 2. Stay alert for extended rainfall and subsequent flooding even after the Typhoon or tropical storm has ended.\10 3. If you have become separated from your family, use your family communications plan or check the Emergency Numbers Plan.\10 4. If you evacuated, return home only when officials say it is safe.\10 5. Drive only if necessary and avoid flooded roads and washed-out bridges.\10 6. Stay off the streets. If you must go out watch for fallen objects; downed electrical wires; and weakened walls, bridges, roads, and sidewalks.\10 7 .Keep away from loose or dangling power lines and report them immediately to the power company.\10 8. Walk carefully around the outside your home and check for loose power lines, gas leaks and structural damage before entering.\10 9. Stay out of any building if you smell gas, floodwaters remain around the building or your home was damaged by fire and the authorities have not declared it safe.\10 10. Inspect your home for damage. Take pictures of damage, both of the building and its contents, for insurance purposes. If you have any doubts about safety, have your residence inspected by a qualified building inspector or structural engineer before entering.\10 11. Use battery-powered flashlights in the dark. Do NOT use candles. Note: The flashlight should be turned on outside before entering - the battery may produce a spark that could ignite leaking gas, if present.\10 12. Watch your pets closely and keep them under your direct control. Watch out for wild animals, especially poisonous snakes. Use a stick to poke through debris.\10 13. Avoid drinking or preparing food with tap water until you are sure it’s not contaminated.\10 14. Check refrigerated food for spoilage. If in doubt, throw it out.\10 15. Wear protective clothing and be cautious when cleaning up to avoid injury.\10 16. Use the telephone only for emergency calls.\10 17. NEVER use a generator inside homes, garages, crawlspaces, sheds, or similar areas, even when using fans or opening doors and windows for ventilation. Deadly levels of carbon monoxide can quickly build up in these areas and can linger for hours, even after the generator has shut off.\10 "/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</FrameLayout>
